Lionel Kevin D. Natividad

Angeles City, Pampanga, Philippines | 09063519099 | lionel.natividad@gmail.com

PROFILE

a committed and flexible professional with experience in leadership roles who has transitioned into the field of web development. I have a strong foundation in HTML, CSS, and JavaScript and have a track record of success in management roles. experienced in building aesthetically pleasing, user-friendly, and useful online applications using the Bootstrap and React frameworks.

RELEVANT LINKS & PROFILE

Github: https://github.com/lionelkvn

Portfolio: https://myportfolio-lilac-five-59.vercel.app/

PROJECT EXPERIENCE

KodeGo Full-Stack Web Development Bootcamp

Inknovative Portfolio Website

May 2023-July 2023

- Tools Used: React, JavaScript, and CSS
- Provide back-end, API as well as front-end codes during application development.
- Led the team in building the front-end as well as the backend website from scratch

KEY SKILLS / TECH STACK

- Front-end : HTML, CSS and JavaScript
- Back-end: Node .js and Express.js
- Database: mySQL
- Collaboration Tools: Google Suite, Zoom and Microsoft Office

EDUCATION

KODEGO WEB DEVELOPMENT BOOTCAMP

Full-Stack Web-Development April 2023 – July 2023

Batch: WD62P

HOLY ANGEL UNIVERSITY

Angeles City, Pampanga

Bachelor of Science in Human Resource Development and Management

Batch 2018

WORK EXPERIENCE

LCN Surplus Center and Enterprises

Angeles City, Pampanga

Manager/Supervisor

2018-Present

- Oversee the overall business operations focusing on maximizing smooth and efficient management and resource allocation.
- Manage a robust client network, diligently addressing clients' needs and requests to fulfill their diverse requirements.
- Site inspection prior to equipment and resource deployment.
- Deployment of heavy-equipment operators prior to operations.

JUNIOR CHAMBER INTERNATIONAL ANGELES CITY CULIAT

Vice-President for Community

Angeles City, Pampanga 2024-present

- Develops Strategic Plans for community projects that aligns with the goals of JCI.
- In charge of the overall implementation of local chapter community projects.
- Responsible for building local relationships with other local organizations and partners

Director for Branding

Angeles City, Pampanga 2022-2023

- Oversee that all branding guidelines are enforced in social media postings.
- Ensure consistency of the organization's visual elements (logos, colors, etc.).
- Development and execution of comprehensive brand strategies in alignment with the organization's mission, vision, and values.